http://www.smalldoghumane.org/privacy-policy/

Animal Shelter Atlanta | Rescue Website | Furkids - Georgia’s Animal Rescue & No-Kill Shelter
In Honor
Georgia’s Largest Animal Rescue, No-Kill Shelters and Sanctuary.
GO
Adopt CatsAdoptable CatsAdoption PromotionsApplicationCage-Free Cat ShelterAdoption CentersRecent AdoptionsAbout FIVAdoption FAQ'sAdopt a Cat Today!Be a part of the Furkids revolution! Adopt a cat today and make a difference.Adopt TodayRecent AdoptionsBe a part of the Furkids revolution! Adoption StoriesView Our BlogDo something fun and read the blog.Adopt DogsAdoptable DogsAdoption PromotionsAdoption SurveyDog Shelter Adoption NewsAdoption FAQ'sAdopt a Dog Today!Be a part of the Furkids revolution! Adopt a dog today and make a difference.Adopt TodayRecent AdoptionsSee some of our recent adoptions.View Our BlogDo something fun and read the blog.VolunteerVolunteer InformationBecome a VolunteerFoster a FurkidGroup OpportunitiesCorporate GroupsYouth OpportunitiesProgramsVolunteer for FurkidsBe a part of the Furkids revolution! Volunteer today and make a difference.VolunteerFoster A FurkidBe a part of the Furkids foster program.  Get involved with the fun today!Learn MoreGroup OpportunitiesFind out how your group can get involved and be part of the Furkids revolution!Learn MoreAboutAbout UsMission and HistoryLocations and HoursContact UsPartners & SponsorsFinancial InformationStatisticsEmployment OpportunitiesLeadershipFAQ'sResourcesDonor PolicyA Home of Our OwnLike, Follow and Share!
Sign Up for our Newsletter
View Our BlogDo something fun and read the blog.News & EventsNewsroomEventsBlogBackgrounderNewslettersGalleryVideosPaws for CocktailsDonate Today
$25
$100
$500
Other
$50
$250
$1000
Sign Up for our Newsletter
ShopFurkids MerchandiseThrift StoreCartMy AccountDonate Today
$25
$100
$500
Other
$50
$250
$1000
Sign Up for our Newsletter
Like, Follow and Share!
Thrift StoresDonateMake a DonationGive a Tribute GiftWish ListDonate to Our Thrift StoresHonorary & Tribute MessagesBequests & Planned GivingGiving PartnersOther Donation OptionsImpact ReportDonate Today
$25
$100
$500
Other
$50
$250
$1000
Make a Tribute GiftAn Honorary Tribute gift is a great way to memorialize your loved ones.
Give a Tribute NowView Our Impact ReportView Impact ReportView Our WishlistGive through our Amazon Wish list portal and directly support a great cause!View the Wish List
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?We collect information from you when you place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, or fill out a form.When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, or credit card information.  You may, however, visit our site anonymously.What do we use your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:To process transactions.  Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
To send periodic e-mails.  The e-mail address you provide for order processing will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future e-mails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each e-mail.How do we protect your information?We offer the use of a secure server.  All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer  (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our database to be accessed only by those authorized with special access rights to our systems and are required to keep the information confidential.After a transaction, your private information will not be kept on file for more than 60 days.Document Retention and Destruction PolicyDo we use cookies?No, we do not use cookies.Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personal identifiable information.  This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.  We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.  However, non-personal identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third Party LinksOccasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website.  These third party sites have separate and independent privacy polices.  We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites.  Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceWe are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act).  We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age.  Our website, products, and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old.Online Privacy PolicyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Your ConsentBy using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy PolicyIf we decide to change our privacy policy we will post those changes on this page.Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us:Furkids, Inc.
P.O. Box 191102
Atlanta, GA  31119
info@furkids.org
770-613-0880
Sign Up for our Newsletter
AdoptDog AdoptionsCat AdoptionsDonateGive a Tribute GiftThrift StoresWish ListVolunteerGroup ProgramsYouth ProgramsEventsBlogNewsAbout UsContactOur MissionPrivacy Policy
Cat Shelter & Headquarters :: 5235 Union Hill Road :: Cumming, GA 30040
Dog Shelter	::
1520 Union Hill Road
::
Alpharetta, GA
30005Copyright 2020 Furkids.
All Rights Reserved.
Web Development by Jumpstart
×Close
Previous
This text will be overwritten by jQuery
Next
Help Save More~ Please Donate Today! ~SUPPORT FURKIDSContinue to Site
Adopt CatsAdoptable CatsAdoption PromotionsApplicationCage-Free Cat ShelterAdoption CentersRecent AdoptionsAbout FIVAdoption FAQ'sAdopt DogsAdoptable DogsAdoption PromotionsAdoption SurveyDog Shelter Adoption NewsAdoption FAQ'sVolunteerVolunteer InformationBecome a VolunteerFoster a FurkidGroup OpportunitiesCorporate GroupsYouth OpportunitiesProgramsAboutAbout UsMission and HistoryLocations and HoursContact UsPartners & SponsorsFinancial InformationStatisticsEmployment OpportunitiesLeadershipFAQ'sResourcesDonor PolicyA Home of Our OwnNews & EventsNewsroomEventsBlogBackgrounderNewslettersGalleryVideosPaws for CocktailsShopFurkids MerchandiseThrift StoreCartMy AccountThrift StoresDonateMake a DonationGive a Tribute GiftWish ListDonate to Our Thrift StoresHonorary & Tribute MessagesBequests & Planned GivingGiving PartnersOther Donation OptionsImpact Report
